# Dinh Duy Kha

PhD Student @ Sungkyunkwan University, South Korea

## Introduction

I am a third-year Ph.D. student advised by Prof. Hojoon Lee at System Security Lab, Sungkyunkwan University. I do research in Systems Security. My research interests include software security, operating systems security, trusted execution environments, and virtualization.

#### EXPERIENCES

System Security Lab, Sungkyunkwan University (SKKU)

Suwon, South Korea 2019 - Present

Graduate Student Researcher

- Design security mechanisms that utilize modern hardware features.
- Design system-level mitigations against side-channels.

VNG Corporation

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam Jun 2018 - Jun 2019

Software Engineering Intern

• Develop and maintain backend APIs for the TalkTV streaming platform written in C (now discontinued).

#### EDUCATION

SUNGYUNKWAN UNIVERSITY
PhD in System Security
Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology
B.S. in Computer Science

Suwon, South Korea 2019 - present Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam 2014 - 2019

### Projects

SIMILATION FRAMEWORK FOR PIM-BASED CONFIDENTIAL COMPUTING

- Use gem5 to perform a full-system simulation of the emerging PIM hardware.
- Implemented security features to allow PIM to be used as an accelerator for confidential computing.

#### CRYPTOGRAPHIC CAPABILITIES FOR PROGRAM COMPARTMENTALIZATION

- Designed an in-process capability-based compartmentalization framework that uses new ARM hardware features and evaluated its security.
- Developed LLVM compiler instrumentation passes to enforce its security policies on memory accesses.
- Developed a kernel module to support the isolation of file-related objects.

#### ACCELERATING ADDRESSSANTIZERS IN RUST

• Designed and formalized the cross-IR compiler analyses that help classify safe, unsafe, and potentially unsafe memory accesses.

## **PUBLICATION**

- [1] **Duy, K. D.**, Noh, T., Huh, S., Lee, H., "Confidential machine learning computation in untrusted environments: A systems security perspective," *IEEE Access*, vol. 9, pp. 168656–168677, 2021. DOI: 10.1109/ACCESS.2021.3136889.
- [2] Dinh Duy, K., Cho, K., Noh, T., Lee, H., "Capacity: Cryptographically-enforced in-process capabilities for modern arm architectures," in *Proceedings of the 2023 ACM SIGSAC Conference on Computer and Communications Security*, ser. CCS '23, ¡conf-loc¿, ¡city¿Copenhagen¡/city¿, ¡country¿Denmark¡/country¿, ¡/conf-loc¿: Association for Computing Machinery, 2023, pp. 874–888, ISBN: 9798400700507. DOI: 10.1145/3576915.3623079. [Online]. Available: https://doi.org/10.1145/3576915.3623079.
- [3] **Duy, K. D.**, Lee, H., "Se-pim: In-memory acceleration of data-intensive confidential computing," *IEEE Transactions on Cloud Computing*, vol. 11, no. 3, pp. 2473–2490, 2023. DOI: 10.1109/TCC. 2022.3207145.
- [4] Cho, K., Kim, J., **Duy, K. D.**, Lee, H., "Rustsan: Retrofitting addresssanitizer for efficient sanitization of rust (to appear)," in 33nd USENIX Security Symposium (USENIX Security 24), USENIX Association, 2024.

Last updated: December 15, 2023